<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The Commonplace Book</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io</link>
<description>This is my personal webpage. I built it because I want to be in a decentralized, free, open and democratic internet. It is a personal blog and about everything and nothing.</description>

<item>
<title>Been Busy</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/10-beenBusy.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/10-beenBusy.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2023 15:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>Been Busy</h2>
            <p>This is a personal post and not really what I intend to write about but it is high time that I post
                something even if it is not what I plan for this website. I have been exceptionally busy the last couple
                of weeks.</p>
            <p>First, we had a family reunion down in Houston over Memorial Day weekend. For my non-US readers, Memorial
                Day is the last monday in May. It is holiday to honour our war dead. Houston is roughly an eight hour
                drive from our home. So, I had two days of driving out of a four day weekend.</p>
            <p>Secondly, we had a couple of family members end up in the hospital after the holiday. They are fine now,
                or at least on the mend.</p>
            <p>Thirdly, I bought a truck on my way home from the reunion. We had delivery plans for the truck but due to
                the hospital stays of family mentioned above those plans went kaput. We ended up flying to Houston,
                picking up the truck, and driving it back home in the space of 24 hours the very next weekend.</p>
            <p>Fourthly, my boss ended up going to the hospital for a grand total of eight days. So I was left in the
                dubious position of running the shop for a few days.</p>
            <p>And finally, I had a friend and mentor pass away this week.</p>
            <p>To say the least of it I have been very busy the last couple of weeks. I think things are calming down
                and I'll get back to keeping this up a little better.</p>



            <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                <p>Home</p>
            </a><h2>Been Busy</h2>
            <p>This is a personal post and not really what I intend to write about but it is high time that I post
                something even if it is not what I plan for this website. I have been exceptionally busy the last couple
                of weeks.</p>
            <p>First, we had a family reunion down in Houston over Memorial Day weekend. For my non-US readers, Memorial
                Day is the last monday in May. It is holiday to honour our war dead. Houston is roughly an eight hour
                drive from our home. So, I had two days of driving out of a four day weekend.</p>
            <p>Secondly, we had a couple of family members end up in the hospital after the holiday. They are fine now,
                or at least on the mend.</p>
            <p>Thirdly, I bought a truck on my way home from the reunion. We had delivery plans for the truck but due to
                the hospital stays of family mentioned above those plans went kaput. We ended up flying to Houston,
                picking up the truck, and driving it back home in the space of 24 hours the very next weekend.</p>
            <p>Fourthly, my boss ended up going to the hospital for a grand total of eight days. So I was left in the
                dubious position of running the shop for a few days.</p>
            <p>And finally, I had a friend and mentor pass away this week.</p>
            <p>To say the least of it I have been very busy the last couple of weeks. I think things are calming down
                and I'll get back to keeping this up a little better.</p>



            <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                <p>Home</p>
            </a>]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Emetophobia</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/09-emetophobia.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/09-emetophobia.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:34:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>Emetophobia</h2>
            <p>Ok, I really can not do a better job at this than the wikipedians so let me just quote some of their <a
                    href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emetophobia">article:</a></p>

            <blockquote>
                <p>Emetophobia is a phobia that causes overwhelming, intense anxiety pertaining to vomit. This specific
                    phobia can also
                    include subcategories of what causes the anxiety, including a fear of vomiting or seeing others
                    vomit. Emetephobes
                    might also avoid the mentions of "barfing", vomiting, "throwing up", or "puking."</p>

                <p>It is common for those who suffer from emetophobia to be underweight or malnourished due to strict
                    diets and
                    restrictions they make for themselves. The thought of someone possibly vomiting can cause the phobic
                    person to engage in
                    extreme behaviors to escape from their anxiety triggers, e.g. going to great lengths to avoid
                    situations that could be
                    perceived as "threatening".</p>

                <p>Emetophobia is clinically considered an "elusive predicament" because limited research has been done
                    pertaining to it. The fear of vomiting receives little attention compared to other fears.</p>

                <p>The event of vomiting may make anyone with this peculiar phobia flee the scene. Some may fear other
                    people throwing up,
                    while others may fear themselves throwing up. Some may fear both. Some may have anxiety that makes
                    them feel as if they
                    will throw up when they actually might not. Other possible fears that may come with emetophobia is
                    not being able to
                    locate a restroom in a timely manner, not being able to stop throwing up, choking on vomit, being
                    embarrassed due to the
                    situation, or having to seek medical attention. People with emetophobia usually experience anxiety;
                    they often may
                    scream, cry, or if it is severe, pass out when someone or something has vomited.</p>
            </blockquote>

            <p>The article goes on to show how emtophobia alters the lifestyle of the Emetophobes. Some have some
                complicated rituals like washing their food several times while they prepare it to avoid foodborne
                illnesses. As a result they do not go out to eat vey often.</p>

            <p>They are so afraid of vomit that they will not go to social situations where alcohol might be served. It
                says some women avoid pregnancy because they are afraid of the morning sickness of the first trimester.
            </p>

            <p>Wow, parenthood must be a bitch for these folks.</p>





            <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                <p>Home</p>
            </a>]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Debutante</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/08-The-Debutante.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/08-The-Debutante.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[ <h2>The Debutante</h2>
            <p>Let me just say "Wow!" here. <a
                    href="https://www.audible.com/pd/The-Debutante-Audiobook/B0BV13NMBK?eac_link=OmB41KBjRfwK&ref=web_search_eac_asin_1&eac_selected_type=asin&eac_selected=B0BV13NMBK&qid=Yen6kSpLkq&eac_id=147-2266999-2520525_Yen6kSpLkq&sr=1-1">The
                    Debutante</a> is an Audible podcast by Jon Ronson. It is the story of a Tulsa debutante's fall from
                society to neo-naziism in the timeframe of the Oklahoma City Bombing. Carol Rowe, the debutante, was
                raised in the upper crust society of Tulsa Oklahoma and after high school she fell in with the wrong
                crowd and hung around with various high profile people in the white supremacist movement. She had ties
                to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elohim_City,_Oklahoma">Elohim City</a> and more than likely
                knew Timothy McVeigh prior to the OKC bombing.</p>

            <p>Somewhere along the way she became an informant for the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (ATF)
                and may have provided the government with information of the planned terrorist act long before the
                events of 19 April 1995.</p>

            <p>Like everything in this type of study there are no definitive conclusions. She may have been a good guy
                acting like a bad guy to get info for the government. She may have been a bad guy stinging along
                everybody that ever came in contact with her. The ambiguity makes for good conspiracy theory copy.</p>

            <p>While I am not too sure what I think about Carol Rowe this story is engaging and was a great listen once
                I got used to Ronson's bizarre accent. Also, I learned quite a bit that I didn't know about the OKC
                Bombing. It is one of those free-to-members things on Audible so give it a listen.</p>


            <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                <p>Home</p>
            </a>]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Unknown Warrior</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/07-The-Unknown-Warrior.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/07-The-Unknown-Warrior.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>The Unknown Warrior</h2>
            <p>Yesterday I started listening to Stephen Fry's podcast <a
                    href="https://www.audible.com/pd/Stephen-Frys-Secrets-of-the-Roaring-20s-Podcast/B0BMHSFWCX?qid=1684596149&sr=1-18&ref=a_search_c3_lProduct_1_18&pf_rd_p=83218cca-c308-412f-bfcf-90198b687a2f&pf_rd_r=FNCC5XQDXZ0GP7DCA6N2&pageLoadId=Lo68nwlyudEFBGIf&creativeId=0d6f6720-f41c-457e-a42b-8c8dceb62f2c">The
                    Secrets of the Roaring Twenties.</a> In the first episode of the series Fry with his usual
                tongue-in-cheek manner sets the stage for the series by providing an overview of the 1920's and most of
                what we think went on in the 20's was a result of the catastrophe of The Great War. I, for one, happen
                to believe that The Great War quite literally changed the world forever. Fry hits on this theme in
                tangentially and the starts telling stories that occured in the year 1920.</p>

            <p>After a couple of stories he went on to explain the origin of "The Unknown Warrior." Early in the war the
                military commands had decided to bury the dead where they died. It was not until after the war when
                families began requesting that the military retrieve the remains of their fallen husbands, sons, and
                brothers the the military realised that families needed closure. The entire nation was in mourning and
                did not have the comfort of having the remains or a funeral service.</p>

            <p>Retrieving the remains of all the fallen would have been a monumental task. One which a post-war United
                Kingdom was incapable of doing. Someone (I think Fry mentions a Reverend David Railton an Army chaplain)
                came up with the idea of retrieving one soldier's remains from a battlefield bringing him back to the UK
                and burying him and providing a closure for the nation.</p>

            <p>The entire process is detailed in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Unknown_Warrior">this
                    wikipedia article</a> and <a
                    href="https://www.westminster-abbey.org/abbey-commemorations/commemorations/unknown-warrior"> at the
                    Westminster Abbey site.</a> I will not even attempt to redo what is so beautifully written on these
                sites.</p>




            <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                <p>Home</p>
            </a>]]>
</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Site Changes</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/06-SiteChanges.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/06-SiteChanges.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 14:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>Site Changes</h2>
            <!-- <h3>Main Stuff</h3> -->
            <!-- <h4>Main Stuff</h4> -->
            <!-- <h5>Main Stuff</h5> -->
            <!-- <h6>Main Stuff</h6> -->

        <p>Life finally slowed down enough for me to spend some time on this site and get it out to the world. Truth is, that I probably had plenty of time to work on this site but I got sidetracked by other shiny toys like <a href="https://gemini.circumlunar.space/">Gemini</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mastodon_(social_network)">Mastodon</a>.</p>
            
        <h3>Site Hosted on Github</h3>

        <p>I finally made a decision and put this site on the air! Yes, if you read some of the older posts on here you will discover that I wanted to avoid entanglements with evil comapnies in the big-tech world and wanted to host this on a server sitting on my desk at home. I still do.</p>

        <p>However, I simply do not have the time to mess with that right now. I wanted to get on with my experiment in simpler internetting and even simpler computing. I do not have to leave my text editor to post directly to github.</p>

        <p>I can hear a ton of people screaming in the background screaming about github now being owned by Microsoft. I know, I know, but really! I am a fat, half-deaf, half-blind guy approaching old age. I am a joke as a computer hacker or political malcontent. What threat am I to anybody? It will not take them long to get bored watching me.</p>

        <h3>Gemini</h3>

        <p>To tell the truth, I really like the idea of Gemini. It is so simple and unadorned that it really is beautiful. It follows my basic idea of everyone having a webpage, an RSS feed, and an email. Gemini is also a quieter place than the WWW. It is a little more laid back. A little more like me.</p>

        <p>I would rather just use Gemini because it is fun to use and the people there are great but it requires a browser of it's own and it is not all that easy for people with negligible computer skills to use. I can not see many of the people that I know IRL ever joining the Gemini world. Most would rather be in Facebook land.</p>

        <p>I have decided to quit making things hard on myself and come back to WWW.</p>

<h3>Mastodon</h3>

<p>A very long time ago when I first got online I wanted to use the internet to become a famous writer. I did not understand how the "web" worked and kind of bounced around from one thing to another for quite a few years not really sure how to become famous online. Then the "social" media things appeared and I thought it was my ticket. I can put my writing in a blog and then use "social" media to promote it.</p>

<p>Well, in my case "social" media became it's own cause in my life. My writing took a backseat to the online presence which took over my life. I would spend hours just maintaining my "social" media presence and wrote nothing of any value. As "social" media grew more toxic I began to retreat from it. I dropped all the big named services a few years ago but kept a couple of the smaller and geekier versions of them.</p>

<p>One of those services was the Twitter-clone Mastodon. It has been a couple of years since I was very active on Mastodon. As I was getting this website online I thought, you know what, I need to post to my Mastodon posse that I am starting a website. I was thinking that doing that might get my website off to a good start and that I might be at least a little social online again.</p>

<p>I got up this morning and took a good long look at Mastodon and came to the conclusion that I do not need to be involved in that nonsense. It is chock full of politics, religion, and the batshit crazy. It might be worse than the big named "social" services out there.</p>

<h3>Back to Simplicity</h3>

<p>So I am going back to the original idea of a webpage, an RSS feed, and email as a social platform.</p>]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>About</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/01-about.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/01-about.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2023 15:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>About</h2>
            <!-- <h3>Main Stuff</h3> -->
            <!-- <h4>Main Stuff</h4> -->
            <!-- <h5>Main Stuff</h5> -->
            <!-- <h6>Main Stuff</h6> -->

            <article>
                <h3>Preface</h3>
                <p> The other day I wrote a rather long rant that was about the reasons why I am doing this. Upon
                    rereading it last night I came to the conclusion that it really is incoherent drivel. So I am
                    rewriting it right now. For those that happened to see the pre-production of this I apologize for
                    this but I need to write something better.</p>
                <h3>Main Event</h3>

                <p>The dream that was the internet has died. The internet was dreamed up to be a nuclear war proof
                    communication system for the government that was decentralized. Even if one node went down it would
                    still work. Civilians got ahold of it and added to the dream. The internet became not only a
                    decentralized communications network but a haven for democracy, openness, and some creativity. </p>

                <p>The internet operated that way for quite a few years. Slowly but surely, a few tech companies began
                    to realize the potential of monetizing the net. This too began to happen. In time a few big tech
                    companies essentially seized control of the internet and the web and transformed it into a
                    centralized totalitarian state with few freedoms.</p>

                <p>This web site is a protest against that.</p>

                <p>Several years ago I was talking with a friend and he said that "X, Y, and Z should happen and then
                    everything will be roses and unicorn farts. I was in a snarky mood that day and said something to
                    the effect that what needed to happen was that everyone needed to get a personal website, use RSS to
                    follow each other, and use email for communication and file transfers. Then, I said, everything will
                    be roses and unicorn farts.</p>

                <p>It took me a few years to realize the beauty of my snarky comment. It took me a while to see that it
                    was a decentralized system and that it was democratic, open, and would allow for creativity. Now I
                    am a believer and am putting my mouth where my money is.</p>

                <p>I will not try to explain all of the vision in this article. It will take me several articles to get
                    it all sorted out in my brain and written out for you. </p>

                <p>What you need to know for know is:
                <ul>
                    <li>This site and all contents by me are Copyright &copy; 2023 by James D. Morgan and is licensed <a
                            href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/">CC-BY 4.0.</a> That means you can use it
                        as
                        long as you tell folks that it is mine.</li>
                    <li>This site will only use <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_file_format">Open
                            formats</a> </li>
                    <li>This is a personal web site which means I may write on just about anything EXCEPT politics and
                        religion.</li>
                    <li>I NEITHER WANT NOR COLLECT ANY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, except maybe your email address so
                        I can respond to you if you write me.</li>
                    <li></li>
                </ul>
                </p>
                <p>On a personal not let me thank you for stopping by and I hope you enjoy what you see here.</p>


                <a href="../index.html" class="linkspage">
                    <p>Home</p>
                </a>]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Fonts</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/04-fonts.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/04-fonts.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h3>Fonts</h3>
                <h6>Added <time datetime="2023-01-24">2023-01-24</time> </h6>

                <p>I learned a nifty little trick today. I have always though it would be a good idea to have the fonts
                    local. I kind of hate third party calls on the web. Somewhere in the back of my head I think that
                    everything pertaining to a webpage, like stylesheets, scripts, images, etc, should be on the local
                    device. You know, under the hood. A car doesn't need to send out for a carburetor after all. If it
                    did the car might be kind of on the slow side. I
                    might be wrong but I think this will speed up a page and maybe keep from pounding the internet so
                    hard. If that makes any sense.</p>

                <p>Anyway, the font for this page was found at <a
                        href="https://fontlibrary.org/en/font/glacial-indifference">Font Library.</a>
                    Yesterday, I noticed at the top right of the page that there was a download link for the fonts. Ok
                    COOL! Now what?!
                </p>

                <p>I ventured over to our beloved StackOverflow and found <a
                        href="https://stackoverflow.com/questions/7961721/how-do-i-install-a-custom-font-on-an-html-site">this
                        little
                        gem.</a></p>

                <p>Basically, all I did was:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>1. Download the zip file.</li>
                    <li>2. Created a "fonts" directory in the directory where my website lives</li>
                    <li>3. Unzip the downloaded file into the fonts directory</li>
                    <li>4. Added these lines to my CSS file (NOTE: the names and folder locations are specific to my
                        setup and fonts, probably not yours): <br>
                        <section class="code-block"> <code>@font-face {
                font-family: "GlacialIndifference";
                src: url('../fonts/GlacialIndifference/OTF/GlacialIndifference-Regular.otf');
                }
                <br>
                <br>
                @font-face {
                font-family: GlacialIndifference;
                font-weight: bold;
                src: url('../fonts/GlacialIndifference/OTF/GlacialIndifference-Bold.otf');
                }</code></section>
                    </li>
                    <li>5. Commented out the link in the header of my HTML file that allows the browser to go pick up
                        the font online.</li>
                </ul>

                <p>After that, for grins and giggles I turned off the internet and checked to see if it worked. <em>IT
                        DID!</em></p>



                <p>I hace seen the "@something" tag in a couple of CSS files that I have perused but I didn't know what
                    it was for. Now I have a whole nuther rabbit hole Fonts]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Links Page</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/02-links.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/02-links.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2023 02:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h2>Links</h2>
<p>NOTE: A WEBPAGE'S INCLUSION ON THIS PAGE IS NOT AN ENDORSEMENT OF THAT PAGE BY ME</p>

<h4>Other Tinkers and Thinkers</h4>
<hr>

<h4>Web Pages</h4>
<hr>
<a href="https://medium.com/matter/the-web-we-have-to-save-2eb1fe15a426" class="linkspage">
<p>The Web We Have To Save</p>
</a>
<p>Written by the "Iranian Blogfather" this article inspired me to abandon social media and go back to
a
simpler time and build a website.</p>

<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2017/12/19/16792306/fcc-net-neutrality-open-internet-history-free-speech-anonymity"
class="linkspage">
<p>We have abandoned every principle of the free and open internet</p>
</a>

<p>An article about how the once open, decentralized, and democratic internet has
disappeared.</p>

<h4>Email</h4>
<hr>
<a href="https://justuseemail.com" class="linkspage">
<p>Just Use Email</p>
</a>
<p>Everybody gripes about it but it is probably the most stable communication platform out
there.</p>
<a href="https://useplaintext.email/" class="linkspage">
<p>Use Plain Text Email</p>
</a>
<p>In spite of my being in general agreement with the above link I do think a little protection might
be
wise.</p>

<h4>RSS</h4>
<hr>
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2018/04/07/rss-is-undead/" class="linkspage">
<p>RSS is Undead</p>
</a>
<p>One of a couple of article that reminded me how cool RSS really is and that I want to keep using
it.</p>
<a href="https://www.artofmanliness.com/living/reading/escape-the-algorithm/" class="linkspage">
<p>Escape the Algorithm</p>
</a>
<p>Another good article that reminded me that it was time to dust off the feed reader and get away
from
online social media.</p>

<h4>Web Development</h4>
<hr>
<a href="https://brutalist-web.design/" class="linkspage">
<p>Brutalist Web Design</p>
</a>
<p>How to design a website that is not a magazine or funky app but is a website. There is an elegance
in
simplicity.</p>
<a href="https://html.spec.whatwg.org/multipage/named-characters.html" class="linkspage">
<p>HTML Named Character Reference</p>
</a>
<p>You've seen all those weird characters like &copy; and &Afr; and &nleqslant; on a website before.
Here is
how to make the characters.</p>

<a href="https://docs.emmet.io/cheat-sheet/" class="linkspage">
<p>Emmet Cheat Sheet</p>
</a>
<p>Among a whole host of apps out there VS Code uses Emmet shortscuts. Here is a guide.</p>

<h4>Plain Text</h4>
<hr>
<a href="https://plaintextproject.online" class="linkspage">
<p>The Plain Text Project</p>
</a>

<p>Scott Nesbitt no longer maintains this wonderful resource on using plain text in one's daily life
but it
remains online as an historical marker. If the above link ever happens to fail try <a
href="https://scottnesbitt.gitlab.io"> his gitlab repo</a> instead.</p>

<h4>Uncategorized</h4>
<hr>
<a href="http://this.how/googleAndHttp/#1519490480000" class="linkspage">
<p>Google and HTTP</p>
</a>
<p>An argument against Google's (and Firefox's) nagging the user about "secure" websites.</p>
]]>
</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Day of Progress</title>
<link>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/03-day-of-progress.html</link>
<guid>https://ragamuffinjim.github.io/blog/03-day-of-progress.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 15:27:32 GMT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h3>A Day of Progress</h3>
                <h6>Added <time datetime="2023-01-22">2023-01-23</time> </h6>

                <p>Ok, so today has been a day of working on this webpage and I actually made some progress! I had a
                    glitch or two in my stylesheet that I couldn't figure out last night. Those issues are now resolved.
                    I also hated the way I had a pile of files meant to be this site so I got those organized in a way
                    that makes sense to me. Some minor league cosmetic things were changed along the way too.</p>

                <p>My big thing today though was learning a little about <abbr
                        title="Real Simple Syndication">RSS</abbr> and getting the feed written for this site.
                    Or, maybe I should say, written as far as the contents of this site will allow at this point.
                    Somewhere along the way I have written an RSS file before but it has been a long time. It is
                    actually much simpler than I remember and I now have a template for adding items to the feed.</p>

                <p>Every bit of this is being done by hand with a text editor. It is not that I am a glutton for
                    punishment, I want to do this the simplest way possible and I want to know all the ins-and-outs of
                    my own site. The text editor is the best way to do this. I should also add that this site lives on
                    my computer and is vetted before it is uploaded.</p>

                <p>This site will mostly consist of items that can be created and or manipulated in an editor. Because
                    this is a website it will only consist of <abbr title="HyperText Markup Language">HTML</abbr>,
                    </dfn> <abbr title="Cascading Style Sheets">CSS</abbr>, JavaScript, <abbr
                        title="Real Simple Syndication">RSS</abbr> and <abbr title="Scalable Vector Graphic">SVG</abbr>
                    files.
                    HTML is the document itself. CSS files are used to make the document pretty. JavaScript is
                    programming language and is used for various purposes on a website. RSS is a way to distribute your
                    document without your readers having to view your site each day. SVG is a text created image.</p>

                <p>Easy peasy.</p>]]>
</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>